Thrills you'll never guess in the newspaper crime sensation!
Shadows of the Night is a drama film directed by D. Ross Lederman.
Gray plays a reporter trying to unravel a murder involving organized crime.
Lorraine plays the heroine.
Flash, played by Flash the Dog.
Jimmy Sherwood, played by Lawrence Gray.
Molly, played by Louise Lorraine.
Feagan, played by Warner Richmond.
Connelly, played by Tom Dugan.
O'Flaherty, played by Alphonse Ethier.
Shadows of the Night is a 1928 American silent drama film directed by D.
Ross Lederman and written by Robert E.
Hopkins and D.
Ross Lederman.
The film stars Flash the Dog, Lawrence Gray, Louise
Lorraine, Warner Richmond, and Tom Dugan.
It was released on October 26, 1928, by Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer.
A copy of Shadows of the Night is housed at the
Cinémathèque Française in Paris, France.
The tone is emotional.